A Guide to the Joseph Francis Fletcher Papers (1931-1991)
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- Form letter from Robert E. Hoggard, 1969 September 9 (Box-folder 012:076)
- Bob to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1969 September 12 (Box-folder 012:077)
- William R. Crout to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 September 13 (Box-folder 012:078)
- Melvyn H. Schreiber to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 September 15 (Box-folder 012:079)
- Carl Binger to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 September 16 (Box-folder 012:080)
- Bill B. Wilson to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 September 16 (Box-folder 012:081)
- Karl Menninger to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 September 19 (Box-folder 012:082)
- Cathy Cascarelli to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 September 23 (Box-folder 012:083)
- Charles k. Hofling to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, 1969 September 23 (Box-folder 012:084)
- Anson Phelps Stokes, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 September 25 (Box-folder 012:085)
- William E. Myer to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 September 30 (Box-folder 012:086)
- Speaking engagements for [Joseph Fletcher], 1969 September - [1970] June (Box-folder 012:087)
- Warren L. Adams to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 October 1 (Box-folder 012:088)
- David J. Snider to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 October 2 (Box-folder 012:089)
- Charles Martin to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 October 17 (Box-folder 012:090)
- Bruce H. Stewart to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 October 22 (Box-folder 012:091)
- Frank C. Bates to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 October 27 (Box-folder 012:092)
- Charles M. Bounds to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 October 28 (Box-folder 012:093)
- Larry E. Walther to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 October 30 (Box-folder 012:094)
- Elizabeth Brown to Joseph Fletcher, [1969 October] (Box-folder 012:095)
- Gammon Jarrell to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 November 5 (Box-folder 012:096)
- William T. Bodoh to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 November 12 (Box-folder 012:097)
- Daniel L. Newcomb to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 November 18 (Box-folder 012:098)
- Form letter from Leon P. Loechler, 1969 November 19 (Box-folder 012:099)
- Thomas J. Bachmeyer to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 November 26 (Box-folder 012:100)
- Duane J. Estes to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 November 27 (Box-folder 012:101)
- Kenneth Vaux to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 December 2 (Box-folder 012:102)
- Thomas V. Litzenburg, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 December 3 (Box-folder 012:103)
- Garrett Hardin to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 December 4 (Box-folder 012:104)
- L. Murray Cathcart to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 December 5 (Box-folder 012:105)
- Ernest S. Heeren to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 December 5 (Box-folder 012:106)
- Fredrick H. Dennis to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 December 8 (Box-folder 012:107)
- Willis D. Weatherford, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 December 8 (Box-folder 012:108)
- Michael Hamilton to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 December 9 (Box-folder 012:109)
- Michael Bevan to [Joseph Fletcher], 1969 December 10 (Box-folder 012:110)
- Lee Ann Bowman to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 December 10 (Box-folder 012:111)
- Loellen Kirby to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 December 10 (Box-folder 012:112)
- Patrick Romanell to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 December 12 (Box-folder 012:113)
- Gordon G. Bergy to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 December 15 (Box-folder 012:114)
- Lawrence Reichel to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 December 18 (Box-folder 012:115)
- Mochinobu Shinio(?) to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 December 25 (Box-folder 012:116)
- Faculty evaluations for the six Boston divinity schools, 1969 December (Box-folder 012:117)
- Ted Boebun(?) to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], [1969] (Box-folder 013:001)
- Form letter from William J. Briggs, [1969] (Box-folder 013:002)
- Mrs. G. N. Crump to Joseph Fletcher, [1969] (Box-folder 013:003)
- Suzanne Crump to Joseph Fletcher, [1969] (Box-folder 013:004)
- Suzanne Crump to Joseph Fletcher, [1969] (Box-folder 013:005)
- Theodore V. Koepke to Joseph Fletcher, with carbon copy and chaplain school course schedule, [1969], 3 Items (Box-folder 013:0006)
- Material concerning Belmont, Massachusetts, [1969], 3 Items (Box-folder 013:007)
- Steve Moran to Joseph Fletcher, [1969] (Box-folder 013:008)
- Agnes Malone Simpson to Forrest Fletcher, [1969] (Box-folder 013:009)
- Ofelia Villamil to Joseph Fletcher, [1969] (Box-folder 013:010)
- Fran to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], [1960s] January 22 (Box-folder 013:011)
- Yasuyuki Owada to Joseph Fletcher, [1960s] March 17 (Box-folder 013:012)
- Nell Joslin Styron to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], [1960s] May 23 (Box-folder 013:013)
- George L. Paine to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], [1960s] June 19 (Box-folder 013:014)
- Nell Styron to [Joseph Fletcher], [1960s] November 27 (Box-folder 013:015)
- Audience Question Cards on Situation Ethics, [1960s], 48 Items (Box-folder 013:016)
- Course syllabus "Introduction to Christianity," International Christian University, Tokyo, Japan, [1960s] (Box-folder 013:017)
- Orrin Davis to [Joseph Fletcher], [1960s] (Box-folder 013:018)
- Euthanasia Educational Fund contribution envelope, [1960s] (Box-folder 013:019)
- Information on Diane Kennedy and James A. Pike, [1960s] (Box-folder 013:020)
- Robert E. Leake to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], [1960s] (Box-folder 013:021)
- Sally Mengel to Joseph Fletcher, [1960s] (Box-folder 013:022)
- Mabel M. Morrison to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], [1960s] (Box-folder 013:023)
- Kathryn Rockwell to Joseph Fletcher, [1960s] (Box-folder 013:024)
- Zimmers to Joe and Florence [Joseph and Forrest Fletcher], [1960s] (Box-folder 013:025)
- Emily to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], [1960s] (Box-folder 013:026)
- Maurice to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], [1960s] (Box-folder 013:027)
- Morris L. Floyd to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 January 2 (Box-folder 013:028)
- Robert H. Ebert to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 January 6 (Box-folder 013:029)
- Kenneth W. Johnson to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 January 7 (Box-folder 013:030)
- Gloria Landahl to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 January 8 (Box-folder 013:031)
- Rex R. Dolan to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 January 14 (Box-folder 013:032)
- Harriet F. Pilpel to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 January 14 (Box-folder 013:033)
- Pirkko Siira to Joseph Fletcher, (two copies), 1970 January 16 (Box-folder 013:034)
- [ ] to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1970 January 20 (Box-folder 013:035)
- Dennis Cross to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 January 23 (Box-folder 013:036)
- Henry K. Beecher to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 January 26 (Box-folder 013:037)
- Trevor Watt to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 January 26 (Box-folder 013:038)
- Harold R. Weaver to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 January 27 (Box-folder 013:039)
- James E. Allen to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 January 28 (Box-folder 013:040)
- Graham B. Blaine, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 January 28 (Box-folder 013:041)
- Steven C. Jackson to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 January 28 (Box-folder 013:042)
- Dee Barrett to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1970 January 29 (Box-folder 013:043)
- Joseph Fletcher to Walcott [B. Thompson], 1970 January 29, February 2 (Box-folder 013:044)
- J. Russell Elkinton to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 January 30 (Box-folder 013:045)
- James W. Knauf to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 January 30 (Box-folder 013:046)
- Peter H. John to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 January 31 (Box-folder 013:047)
- Frank C. Bates to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosures, 1970 February 3, 5 Items (Box-folder 013:048)
- Isaac Asimov to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 February 5 (Box-folder 013:049)
- Doris A. Harland to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 February 5 (Box-folder 013:050)
- Sister Maria Lugosi to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 February 5 (Box-folder 013:051)
- John Miller Horton to Joe and Forrest [Joseph and Forrest Fletcher], with enclosure, 1970 February 6, N.D., 2 Items (Box-folder 013:052)
- Sister Theresa Corcoran to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 February 10 (Box-folder 013:053)
- John A. T. Robinson to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 February 10 (Box-folder 013:054)
- Robert D. Schieler to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 February 11 (Box-folder 013:055)
- Thomas K. Morse to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 February 13 (Box-folder 013:056)
- Mary Schwendeman to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 February 14 (Box-folder 013:057)
- Theodore V. Koepke to Joseph Fletcher, with copy, 1970 February 16, 2 Items (Box-folder 013:058)
- John H. Nichols to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 February 18 (Box-folder 013:059)
- Chris Smith to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 February 18 (Box-folder 013:060)
- Dibinga Wa Said to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1970 February 19 (Box-folder 013:061)
- W. Gordon Ross to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 February 20 (Box-folder 013:062)
- Luke L. H. Cheung to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, 1970 February 21 (Box-folder 013:063)
- Hans Weissgerber to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure, 1970 February 23, 2 Items (Box-folder 013:064)
- Prohuman Williams to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure, 1970 February 23 (Box-folder 013:065)
- Frank C. Bates to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 February 26 (Box-folder 013:066)
- Samuel D. Freeman to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure, 1970 February, 2 Items (Box-folder 013:067)
- Raymond J. Shuster to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 March 1 (Box-folder 013:068)
- Time magazine essay: "Radical Saul Alinsky: Prophet of Power," 1970 March 2 (Box-folder 013:069)
- William H. Turpie to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 March 5 (Box-folder 013:070)
- Joyce Strah to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 March 6 (Box-folder 013:071)
- Legal release for broadcast, 1970 March 10 (Box-folder 013:072)
- Hays to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1970 March 11 (Box-folder 013:073)
- James H. Grace to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 March 12 (Box-folder 013:074)
- Harold R. Weaver to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 March 13 (Box-folder 013:075)
- James G. Newbill to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 March 15 (Box-folder 013:076)
- Elmer S. West, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 March 20 (Box-folder 013:077)
- Foy Valentine to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 March 26 (Box-folder 013:078)
- John A. Harms to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 March 31 (Box-folder 013:079)
- Form letter from Laura Hembree and Brenda Lenox, 1970 March (Box-folder 013:080)
- Donald I. Rice to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 April 9 (Box-folder 013:081)
- O. Dean Nelson to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 April 10 (Box-folder 013:082)
- Florence Lichtenberger to Rollin T. Fairbanks, with note by [Fairbanks] to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 May 13, 2 Items (Box-folder 013:0)
- George W. Barrett to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1970 May 18 (Box-folder 013:084)
- Gerald H. Richards to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 May 18 (Box-folder 013:085)
- David C. Anger to [Joseph Fletcher], 1970 May 21 (Box-folder 013:086)
- Marvin Kohl to [Joseph Fletcher], 1970 June 3 (Box-folder 013:087)
- Dan Ferry to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 June 4 (Box-folder 013:088)
- William A. Coolidge to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 June 9 (Box-folder 013:089)
- G. H. Parke-Taylor to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 June 11 (Box-folder 013:090)
- Frank M. Oppenheim to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 June 15 (Box-folder 013:091)
- Wilfred Myll to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 June 20 (Box-folder 013:092)
- John A. T. Robinson to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 October 26 (Box-folder 013:093)
- John A. T. Robinson to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 November 11 (Box-folder 013:094)
- Bill [William B. Spofford?] to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1970 November 20 (Box-folder 013:095)
- Henry M. Shires to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1970 November (Box-folder 013:096)
- Henry Bird to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1970 December 9 (Box-folder 013:097)
- John B. Martin to Ruth Russell, with note by Russell to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 December 17 (Box-folder 013:098)
- Sachiko Yoshizawa to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 December 26 (Box-folder 013:099)
- Forrest and Joseph Fletcher to Ann and Thomas H. Hunter, 1970 December (Box-folder 013:100)
- John to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], [1970 December] (Box-folder 013:101)
- Retirement(?) card for Joseph Fletcher, [1970?] (Box-folder 013:102)
- Forrest [Fletcher] to Anne [Hunter], 1976 January 16 (Box-folder 014:001)
- Forrest [Fletcher] to Anne [Hunter], 1976 January 31 (Box-folder 014:002)
- Forrest [Fletcher] to Ann and Tom [Anne and Thomas H. Hunter], [1976] February 5 (Box-folder 014:003)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom and Ann [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1976 February 5 (Box-folder 014:004)
- Valentines to Anne and {Thomas H. Hunter] from [Forrest Fletcher], 1976 February (Box-folder 014:005)
- Forrest [Fletcher] to Ann and Tom [Anne and Thomas H. Hunter], 1976 March 4, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:006)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], with enclosure, 1976 December 8, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:007)
- Roger E. Stevenson to Margery W. Shaw, 1977 March 15 (Box-folder 014:008)
- Catherine Damme to Joseph Fletcher, 1977 May 11 (Box-folder 014:009)
- Michael Bayles to Joseph Fletcher, 1977 July 8 (Box-folder 014:010)
- Hardy Jones to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure, 1977 July 26, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:011)
- Forrest [Fletcher] to Annie [Anne Hunter], 1977 July 29 (Box-folder 014:012)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1977 September 29 (Box-folder 014:013)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1977 October 6 (Box-folder 014:014)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1977 November 18 (Box-folder 014:015)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1977 November 30 (Box-folder 014:016)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1977 December 9 (Box-folder 014:017)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1977 December 24 (Box-folder 014:018)
- Forrest and Joe [Forrest and Joseph Fletcher] to Annie and Tom [Anne and Thomas H. Hunter], 1977 December (Box-folder 014:019)
- Gift card to [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1977 December (Box-folder 014:020)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom and Annie [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1978 February 1, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:022)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1978 March 9 (Box-folder 014:023)
- Joseph Fletcher to Paul [Kurtz], 1978 March 31 (Box-folder 014:024)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom and Annie [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1978 April 25 (Box-folder 014:025)
- Paul Kurtz to Joseph Fletcher, 1978 June 1 (Box-folder 014:026)
- Forrest and Joe [Forrest and Joseph Fletcher] to Tom and Annie[Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1978 June 12 (Box-folder 014:027)
- Barbara Bergstrom to Joseph Fletcher, 1978 June 28 (Box-folder 014:028)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], with note by Forrest Fletcher, 1978 June 29 (Box-folder 014:029)
- Materials relative to the publication of Humanhood: Essays in Biomedical Ethics, 1978 July 3, N.D., 6 Items (Box-folder 014:030)
- Paul Kurtz and Morris B. Storer to Joseph Fletcher, 1978 July 17 (Box-folder 014:031)
- Barbara Bergstrom to Joseph Fletcher], with enclosures, 1978 July 20 (Box-folder 014:032)
- Paul Kurtz to Joseph Fletcher, 1978 July 25 (Box-folder 014:033)
- Memorandum from Joseph Fletcher, et al, 1978 September 14 (Box-folder 014:034)
- Joe F. [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1978 September 24 (Box-folder 014:035)
- Charlotte Farley to Joseph Fletcher, 1978 October 18 (Box-folder 014:036)
- Charlotte Farley to Joseph Fletcher, 1978 October 26 (Box-folder 014:037)
- Charlotte Farley to Joseph Fletcher, 1978 October 31 (Box-folder 014:038)
- Marina to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1978 November 1 (Box-folder 014:039)
- Charlotte Farley to Joseph Fletcher, 1978 November 18 (Box-folder 014:040)
- Draft introduction to Humanhood: Essays in Biomedical Ethics, introduction by Thomas H. Hunter, [1978 November?] (Box-folder 014:041)
- [Forrest and Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1978 December 19, 20 (Box-folder 014:042)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Annie [Anne Hunter], 1978 December 22, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:043)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], with note from [Forrest Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1978 December 23 (Box-folder 014:044)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1978 December 28 (Box-folder 014:045)
- [Forrest and Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1978 December (Box-folder 014:046)
- Forrest [Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1978 (Box-folder 014:047)
- Forrest [Fletcher] to Annie [Anne Hunter], 1979 January 4, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:048)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], [1979] January 7, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:049)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], Forrest [Fletcher] to Tom {Thomas H. Hunter], 1979 January 18, 3 Items (Box-folder 014:050)
- Forrest [Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1979 January 28 (Box-folder 014:051)
- Forrest [Fletcher] to Annie and Tom [Anne and Thomas H. Hunter], 1979 May 4 (Box-folder 014:052)
- [Forrest and Joseph Fletcher] to [Anne and Thomas H. Hunter], 1979 September 14 (Box-folder 014:053)
- Annie [Anne Hunter] to Forrest [Fletcher], 1979 October 9 (Box-folder 014:054)
- [Forrest and Joseph Fletcher] to Annie [Anne Hunter], 1979 October 15 (Box-folder 014:055)
- [Forrest and Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1979 December (Box-folder 014:056)
- Joseph Fletcher - Review of Principles of Biomedical Ethics, with attached note by [Fletcher] to [Mary Faith Marshall], [1979] and [1989] (Box-folder 014:057)
- Charles Teel, Jr to Joseph Fletcher, [1970s] March 13 (Box-folder 014:058)
- Sister Jane Tierney to Joseph Fletcher, [1970s] (Box-folder 014:059)
- [ ] to [Joseph Fletcher], [1970s] (Box-folder 014:060)
- [Forrest Fletcher] to [Anne and Thomas H. Hunter; Debbie and Peter Hunter], 1980 January 11, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:061)
- [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. Hunter] and Mary [Wagner], 1980 January 17 (Box-folder 014:062)
- [Joseph Fletcher] to Anne Hunter, 1980 January 20 (Box-folder 014:063)
- [Forrest and Joseph Fletcher] to [Anne and Thomas H. Hunter], 1980 February (Box-folder 014:064)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1980 February (Box-folder 014:065)
- [Forrest Fletcher] to [Anne and Thomas H. Hunter], 1980 March 6 (Box-folder 014:066)
- [Forrest and Joseph Fletcher] to [Anne and Thomas H. Hunter], 1980 September 19 (Box-folder 014:067)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Annie [Anne Hunter], 1980 November 8 (Box-folder 014:068)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1980 December 20 (Box-folder 014:069)
- Annie [Anne Hunter] to [Forrest and Joseph Fletcher], 1980 December 27 (Box-folder 014:070)
- [Forrest Fletcher] to [Anne Hunter], 1980 December (Box-folder 014:071)
- Joseph Fletcher to T. R. Johns, [1980] (Box-folder 014:072)
- Joseph Fletcher to Annie [Anne Hunter], 1981 January 4 (Box-folder 014:073)
- Letters from caroline Kennedy to Joseph Fletcher, 1981 February 21-1983 June 29 (Box-folder 014:074)
- Forrest [Fletcher] to Anne and [Thomas H. Hunter], 1981 February 28 (Box-folder 014:075)
- [Forrest and Joseph Fletcher] to Anne F. Hunter, 1981 April [18] (Box-folder 014:076)
- Joseph Fletcher]to Thomas H. Hunter, [981] May 29 (Box-folder 014:077)
- Photocopies of newspaper clippings: "The Creationsits' Contradictions," by Joseph Fletcher, and "Reverends of Rosedale," by Sam Patten, 1981 June 13, 24 (Box-folder 014:078)
- Joseph Fletcher to Walker Percy, with enclosure, (photocopies), 1981 June 22, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:079)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], with enclosures, 1981 June 30, 4 Items (Box-folder 014:080)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], with a note from [Forrest Fletcher] to [Anne Hunter], 1981 July 29 (Box-folder 014:081)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], with enclosure, 1981 September 13, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:082)
- [Forrest and Joseph Fletcher] to Annie [Anne Hunter], 1981 October 2 (Box-folder 014:083)
- [Forrest and Joseph Fletcher] to [Anne and Thomas H. Hunter], 1982 January 9 (Box-folder 014:84)
- [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], with note by [Forrest Fletcher], 1982 April 12, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:085)
- [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. Hunter], 1982 April 25 (Box-folder 014:086)
- [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. Hunter], 1982 May 27 (Box-folder 014:087)
- [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1982 July 17, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:088)
- [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. Hunter], 1982 August 21 (Box-folder 014:089)
- [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. Hunter], 1982 August 29 (Box-folder 014:090)
- Forrest [Fletcher] to Annie [Anne Hunter], 1982 November 16, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:091)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1982 November 19 (Box-folder 014:092)
- Joseph Fletcher to [Thomas H. Hunter], with a note by [Forrest Fletcher], 1982 November 21 (Box-folder 014:093)
- Material concerning Joseph Fletcher, Jr., 1982, 1983, N.D., 5 Items (Box-folder 014:094)
- [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], with enclosure, 1983 January 9, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:095)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], with enclosure, 1983 January 26, 3 Items (Box-folder 014:096)
- [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1983 February 10 (Box-folder 014:097)
- Forrest [Fletcher] to Annie [Anne Hunter], 1983 February (Box-folder 014:098)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. Hunter], with enclosures, 1983 March 25, 3 Items (Box-folder 014:099)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1983 April 17 (Box-folder 014:100)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1983 May 2 (Box-folder 014:101)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1983 June 7, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:102)
- Note from [Thomas H. Hunter] to Annie [Anne Hunter], with photocopy of Secular Humanism: It's the Adjective That Counts, by Joseph Fletcher, 1983 October 28 (Box-folder 014:103)
- Forrest [Fletcher] to [Anne and Thomas H. Hunter], 1983 November 13, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:104)
- Christmas card from [Joseph and Forrest Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1983 [December] (Box-folder 014:105)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1984 January 7 (Box-folder 014:106)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1984 January 7 (Box-folder 014:106)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. Hunter], 1984 January 21 (Box-folder 014:107)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1984 April 20 (Box-folder 014:108)
- F [Forrest Fletcher] to Annie [Anne Hunter], with enclosures, 1984 April, 3 Items (Box-folder 014:109)
- Joseph Fletcher to Thomas [H.] Hunter, 1984 May 8 (Box-folder 014:110)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Thomas H. Hunter, 1984 August 22 (Box-folder 014:111)
- Memorial card for Joseph Fletcher, Jr., 1984 October 12 (Box-folder 014:112)
- Joe and F. [Joseph and Forrest Fletcher] to [Anne and Thomas H. Hunter], 1984 November 10 (Box-folder 014:113)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom and Annie [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1984 November 16 (Box-folder 014:114)
- F [Forrest Fletcher] to Annie [Anne Hunter], with note by [Joseph Fletcher], 1984 November 29 (Box-folder 014:115)
- Card with new address for Forrest and [Joseph] Fletcher, [1984] (Box-folder 014:116)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1985 February 6 (Box-folder 014:117)
- Forrest and [Joseph Fletcher] to [Anne and Thomas H. Hunter], 1985 March 5 (Box-folder 014:118)
- Pages from Late Imperial China, dedication and bibliography of Joseph Fletcher, Jr., 1985 December (Box-folder 014:119)
- Forrest [Fletcher] to [Anne and Thomas H. Hunter], 1986 January 3 (Box-folder 014:120)
- [Joseph] and Forrest [Fletcher] to [Anne and Thomas H. Hunter], 1986 January 29, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:121)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to [Anne and Thomas H. Hunter], [1986] February 14, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:122)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], with enclosure, 1986 March 7, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:123)
- Dave Bell to Joseph Fletcher, 1986 May 6 (Box-folder 014:124)
- Notes from [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. Hunter], 1986 July 18 (Box-folder 014:125)
- Forrest and [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1986 October 21 (Box-folder 014:126)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1986 November 24, 3 Items (Box-folder 014:127)
- [Joseph Fletcher] to [Anne and Thomas H. Hunter], with note by [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. Hunter], 1986 December 20, 2 Items (Box-folder 014:128)